Hello.
The next thing we want to do is make it so that whenever my character is damaged, the amount of hearts
that they have is removed.
So first of all, if we head over to the Heart Widget region and go over to the graph, I want you to
create a new custom event and you right click for add custom event and just cool this remove part.
Let me call this customer one.
What we're going to do is if we drag in our hot food and forget hot food to struggle here and offset.
Visibility and test visibility to be hidden.
So whenever my placard is damaged, we'll cool this customer event and this will basically hide my harmful
image and we'll see the empty image later on.
We're going to make a healthy cup.
And when my character picks up the help, they're going to be able to recover their lost hearts.
So I need you to create another customer event.
So if you right click and add custom event and call this add part, and when we fire this node, we're
basically just going to copy the data.
And make it so our heart is now visible.
So here under visibility.
Select visible.
Next thing we just compile and save this.
And if we head over to the player.
Hot.
In some free space.
I need you to create a new custom event.
So be right click and add custom event and call it player damaged.
So we're going to call this custom event whenever my character is damaged.
And what we're going to do is basically get the last heart in our pop box and we're going to make it
hidden.
In order to do this.
If we head over to the graph.
We want to get our heart reference and to struggle here and look for length.
And this will get how many items are inside of my heart, Reverend?
So I made my to start with three hearts.
So the length of this heart reference is going to be three.
There's one more thing we need to do.
If we just drag off this length and look for subtract, we need to subtract this from one.
Now, the reason we need to subtract one is kind of similar to the reason we added one here.
Arrays basically count the number zero.
So I made it so my character has three hearts.
So this heart reference is going to be three, but arrays count the number zero.
So the length of this is actually going to be four.
So we need to subtract it by a value of one so that this number accurately shows my parts.
Two my pair character has.
Next if we drag in a reference again.
We need to drag a pet and look for each lip.
And just hook us up here.
So this for each loop node will fire.
However many times my heart references.
So this will fire four times because of count zero one, two and three when this array index.
Equals.
The length of this.
That tells the game that we're referencing our last hall.
So if this array index is three.
And the length of this is three.
This array element is going to be the last hot inside of our hot box.
And when that is true, we're going to remove it from our game.
So if we just drag up here and look for Branch and hook up loop body into here, then if we drag off
this array element and pull the remove heart adjustment that we just made.
Now that we've removed our heart, I want to remove it from my heart reference.
So if we just track in our heart reference, which contains a list of all of our hearts, we can just
drag up here and look for remove item.
And then just double click here and connect us into here.
So later on in my game, we're going to be creating a health pickup system.
So when we pick out some health, we're basically going to add any lost hearts that my player has lost.
So in order to do this, we're going to need to keep track of all the hearts that my player character
has lost.
So on the heart reference, just right click and duplicate it and call it lost heart.
Reference.
Then I want need to draw in this lost heart reference.
And a struggle here I look for at.
And I need you to add this before we remove the heart from the heart reference.
Otherwise, it will be lost forever.
They just hook this up here and make sure it is in front of the bit before we remove it.
Then if we just connect this to here.
And if I could compile, if my character had three help and they were damaged using this node, it's
going to get that last half and called the remove heart, which will make it hidden.
Then we'll add it to our lost heart reference and remove it from our heart reference.
That way, if the player character is damaged again, it won't start counting from the heart that we've
already removed.
Next, if we just close this.